night city is the city of
dreams but
dreams can be
broken corporations are squeezing every
last drop of life from the earth our
dreams our goals our plans all crushed
under the Relentless tread of the
corporate machine this corpo parasite is
controlling governments media
technology and now they're after our
lives and souls hope may be dying but as
long as we live we fight for survival
for dignity for a shred of Freedom we
are outcasts Rebels and Edge Runners we
have nothing to lose it's our
responsibility to stand against arasaka
tyranny understand do whatever it takes
to stop them no matter what no matter
where break in Haack and slash shoot to
kill hell you still don't see it
but you will one
[Music]
day